take this
literally you know in Damascus
and during my father's time when a man
is harmed they actually write his record
on a great week and they hungry
now up for now in during my father's
time his classmates were found and
according to him they put
big proper controls the truth is record
not for him to read but for others to me
they actually hang it on his neck and
the Honey up to now ASAP does it now and
the return repairs
so that is when they don't take his
kidney diseases they take it literally
like the church
foreign
like running dogs and cats it doesn't
really Rain Dogs you don't get it you
get directions behind your back that
just means you have a bad record
s
oh yeah
the reason the reason everybody will be
in hand
initially because God will not be there
in the absence of God with his helps
though but then then God comes
and becomes heaven for the Believers and
becomes a worse Hymn for this video
for everybody else
even Jesus and Muhammad did Morgan well
yeah everybody
everybody yeah
we're told that uh this Alicia's head
will serve to make you appreciated
because you do not appreciate
the good things unless you know about
the bad things in life
exactly
but you see here does not want the
picture to you the fire and this
it's a terrible place but the the table
can get out it's eternity and
hopelessness
so that initial health is not
Eternal and it is not hopeless
go to sort of things to stay you know or
in a more permanent state would be
transient like here
just a transient candle set up for us
mention something uh
they mentioned something in the famous
lyceum cream
which was declared to the Council of
nicaea it says that talking about Jesus
Christ as part of the belief
then he descended into hell and then
ascended into heaven it's very
impressive
Apostles Creed I think uh how would you
decide Jesus Christ
and then he ascended into into heaven
which is very very interesting
you can see that verse
so initially we all go to hell
every single one of you would initially
enter their end
this is an inevitable method decreased
by the law
it is written in the most very powerful
words
by God
yeah
the sun will be taken out I remember
since then we save those to what
righteousness giving the wicked very
humiliated
it's only makes sense because the
sequence of events in the hereafter
is that your dear resurrected first
now when you are resurrected that God is
not there physically when God comes
differently
so the periods of absence of God's
physical presence is in his head
the Purgatory after
Purgatory would be for people who didn't
make it to heaven and didn't make him do
that
people who said
a year and a half before they died
they didn't get the chance to grow
it's 10 seconds
but those people are talking to Quran
they have powers of descendants because
they know they can recognize they know
who are the ones
yeah everybody expresses everybody
this one is
they know by the marks of certain people
they have frustrated they know by the
marks of the other
so they are people of discernment I
don't know if that's reward the people
who have discernment
everybody would recognize Everybody by
their love
sometimes
punishment again
they will sneak into heaven but they
will suffer even worse
because the presence of God
the baby songs suffered more in the
presence of God
in heaven
so when they sneak up to heaven they
come closer to God and they cannot stand
they shatter and they go back
voluntarily they go back to hell
that head is so bad so they sneak back
again they will especially turn it to
yourself to listen
in this way
they keep hoping that maybe you know
they come closer to that they will be
able to stand it but you can so they go
back
thank you
you spend the eternity circulating
between her
and a horse in heaven
that sounds ironic isn't it
so that's why when God comes
the people who saw the grown would
enjoyed to be in heaven automatically
and the ones whose swords are small and
shrunk will suffocate so it rewards here
it's worse than me
and the proof is that they voluntarily
they go back to him
we were
Abdullah
good
no this is
we'll come to you
you know
we all have to love
again
foreign
insurance
because because
maybe we are not
we are Against the Machine ourselves
you know how
Abraham Abraham
he was a great believer even then
from the miracle of Quran in our time
but
I'm sure
sure
in real life
just for yourself
foreign
it would be immersion for the people
unfortunately that the identification
which
issued people if they really
are open if they will open their heart
doesn't see us
trust me you know the question here is
Abraham do you not believe
of course the Abraham don't believe
they are sure
we have a very good example of our group
here
we are we were very very fortunate and
we have the unique
great portion of
having the local Quran come out of this
mosque
to the whole world
proven that every word in this Quran is
from God
it's a very very
Indescribable great
very humbling Discovery and we are
going to realize how great it is
I guess we do we do yeah we don't
realize that we're experience but I'm
sure each one of you met people who say
well we believe the qurans from God you
don't need this
so when I was there saying we are better
than Abraham we don't need the assurance
we did believe that the Quran is from
God before the discovery of this Mercy
in the Quran
but when we saw it our faith strength
like God said in Surah 74 after the
number 19. God says to strengthen the
prayer of the Believers
so our faith was 20
. so this example here of Abraham
Wanted music reassurance
means that the sincere believers
beneath the issue and the quietly
assured that there is nothing wrong with
also the verse here has an actual
incident for Abraham
took four birds and and
started the markings on the birds
and then he cut the birds in pieces and
put them one piece on each on the top of
the hill
spot spot apart
and when you called them God actually
put the birds together
the same Birds this is why he started
the markings Church
of course God had the answers do that it
doesn't have to do with himself
it was all done by his command
so this is an actual incident
showing resurrection of the Dead
and the verse before this you remember
the guy who was resurrected from dead
after 100 years
the belief of Resurrection is very
important
it is it is required along with belief
in God
so we're gonna quit now but if you want
to remind you
[Music]
the more you grow
the higher is your rank for eternity
and
one of the most intensive
worship that make you grow is making
dick
at all
it's it's really a shame to escape
through it
as though
so don't sleep through it
it's not
it's not terrible you know to just wake
up and come to the mosque at six o'clock
in the morning with a very pleasant then
I'm going to open a commemorate the
the
commemoration in a group is also very
effective
because it is
contagious
when one person in the group makes it
that all of us feel
also
there would be a little change tomorrow
and that we used to study Arabic after
the
but uh
the point was made that after that we
were very very high and the Arabic
lessons were really let down
it's not Crashing Down from
very high so we're going to change the
Arabic language lessons to before the
quranic study as of next week
so the people who want to study Arabic
will come
to the mosque at six o'clock
and we study are the complete Cemetery
the Quran
tomorrow there will be no Arabic message
so we can
Hammer up there for Hawaii